Love
Yagami
Light, Ryuuzaki has asked for your help with the investigation.
月、竜崎が捜査協力をして欲しいと言っている、
If you're willing to help, we need you to come here as soon as possible.
やる気があるならすぐに来てくれ
I understand, father.
わかった、父さん
And here I was thinking of how to start discussing the subject with them...
どうやってこっちから切り出すを考えていたのに、
I never imagined that they would approach me with this first.
まさか向こうからきてくれるとは…
In this manner, I'll be able to investigate both the Investigative Headquarters and the fake Kira as much as I want.
これで捜査本部の内情と同時に、
偽キラの事も堂々と調べていける
Whatever it takes, I've got to find the fake Kira before they do.
なんとしても偽キラの事は、
本部の人間より一歩先を知る必要がある
Thank you, Yagami-kun.
ありがとう、夜神君
No problem; after all, we both want to catch Kira, Ryuuga.
いや、キラを捕まえたい気持ちは一緒だよ、流河
ここでは竜崎と呼んでください
Please call me "Ryuuzaki" while you're here.
え？
I'm Matsui.
松井です
I'm Aihara.
相原です
And I'm Asahi.
そして私は朝日だ
I see...
なるほど…じゃあ僕は、朝日月でいいかな
So, does that make me "Asahi Light"?
Yes, That is good.
それでお願いします、
私もここでは月君と呼ぶことにします
While you're here, I'll call you "Light-kun".
Sorry for throwing you in at the deep end, but I need you to look over all the current material we have on the investigation,
では早速ですが、今までのキラに関する捜査資料と、
このテレビ局に送られてきた
一般には未公開のビデオを見てください
including the videos that were sent to the Japanese TV station.
I'm afraid that I can't let you take any of the material away, or make notes of it.
全ての資料等の持ち出しやメモを取る事は、禁止です
Understood.
わかった
In that case, let's begin.
それでは始めます
Light...
月…
Last night
So... we'll proceed by hiding the possibility of a second Kira, and by having Yagami Light assist us with the investigation.
では、第二のキラの可能性は伏せ、
夜神月君に捜査協力してもらうという方向でいきます
B-But won't it be hard for us to investigate with him if we do that?
し、しかし…それでは一緒に捜査しにくいのでは？
He's right. What's the point in him helping us in this investigation anyway?
そうだ、大体何の為の捜査協力だか…
No, we only need to hide this from him till we've heard his opinions on these videos.
いえ、それを隠すのは、
彼にこのビデオを一本見てもらい感想を聞くまでです
Light-kun's skills of deduction are truly quite amazing.
月君の推理力には素晴らしいものがあります、
If he sees these videos, he may be able to deduce that this is the work of a second Kira.
このビデオを見たら、
第二のキラだという推理をしてくれるかもしれません
If he sees these videos, he may be able to deduce that this is the work of a second Kira.
It has to be a second Kira since the victims were ones Kira normally wouldn't have killed, "since they only committed minor crimes",
しかし第二のキラの根拠は、
「予告殺人されたものは、
キラが裁くはずのない罪の軽い者だった」という、
but that's the only basis you have, isn't it Ryuuzaki?
竜崎の推理でしかないですよね
That's not the only reason.
…それだけではありません
Up until now, we've assumed that Kira needs a face and a name in order to kill.
今まで私達が想定してきたキラは、殺人に顔と名前が必要でした
Yet, from the fact that Ukita-san was killed when he happened to rush to the TV station that time...
しかしあの時、
テレビ局にたまたま駆けつけた宇生田さんが殺された事
And from the fact that Kira spoke as if they could kill L merely by having him appear on TV,
L をテレビ出演させれば、殺せる様な言い方をしていることから、
we can come to the conclusion that the second Kira can kill people merely by seeing their faces.
第二のキラは、顔だけで殺せるという事になります
If, after reviewing the case and watching these videos,
要は月君に捜査状況とビデオを見てもらい、
Light-kun is able to deduce that there is a second Kira, the majority of my suspicions against him will be lifted.
第二のキラの可能性があると推理したら、
月君の疑いはほぼ晴れるという事です
What do you mean by that, Ryuuzaki?
どういうことだ、竜崎
It's evident that Kira wants to kill the L who has been leading the police force.
キラなら、捜査本部の指揮を執っている L は
絶対殺したいと思っているはずです
If things continue to progress as they are, I will die after appearing on TV in three days' time.
今のままなら、私は第二のキラの要求通り、
三日後にテレビに出演し死ぬことになります
I doubt that Kira would let an opportunity like this pass.
キラなら
こんな絶好の機会を棒にふる事はしないと思うんです
What if my son doesn't manage to deduce that there is a second Kira?
ではもし、息子が第二のキラの推理をしなければ、
Does it mean that your suspicions will deepen?
疑いが深まると言うのか
いえ、その場合は五パーセント未満のままですし、
No. If that happens, my suspicions will remain at 5% or lower.
We'll reveal to him that we're investigating the possibility of a second Kira, and have him assist us with that.
そのままこちらから、
「第二のキラの線で捜査している」とうちあげて、
協力してもらいます
I believe that you have understood from this that I am Kira.
以上の事から、私が本物のキラだという事がわかったと思います
On the date and time specified...
指定された日時どおりに…
Watching these videos... the terrible quality of them makes me feel sick... is that just because I am the real Kira?
このビデオを見て、出来の悪さに吐き気がするのは、
僕が本物のキラだからか…
This is far more serious than a simple drop in my image as Kira...
まったくキラのイメージダウンどころの話ではない
But why has no one offered any explanations for any of these videos?
しかし何故、このビデオに関しての説明を誰もしてこない…
There's something odd going on here...
何か変だ
Either way, I better not say anything stupid regarding this.
まあ、どちらにしろ、
僕もこのビデオに関しては、下手な事は何も言わない事だ
If I leave things as they are, L will die.
放っておけば L は死ぬんだ…
How is it going, Light-kun? Have you been able to deduce anything from this?
どうですか、月君
何かわかりましたか？
Why you--!
コイツ…
There's a possibility that there's more than one person who has Kira's power.
ちから
キラの能力を持った人間は、一人じゃないかもしれない
K-Kira's power? What are you saying, Light?
ちから
キ、キラの能力は…どういうことだ月
K-Kira's power? What are you saying, Light?
If nothing else, there's a high probability that this is not the same Kira that we've been dealing with until now.
少なくともコイツは、今までのキラじゃない可能性が高い
今までのキラなら、
殺人予告にこんな容疑者を使ったりはしない
The Kira we've been dealing with until now would not have utilized the suspects used in this broadcast.
Add the fact that if Kira does indeed need a name and a face to kill, it's strange that they were able to kill the policemen who merely happened to go to the TV station.
それに、キラの殺人に顔と名前が必要とするなら、
テレビ局に偶然駆けつけた
刑事や警官を殺せたのも、おかしいじゃないか
I-It's the same...
お…同じだ…
The same as L... I mean, that's exactly the same theory as Ryuuzaki!
L …いや、竜崎の推理とまったく同じ…
W-Well done, Light!
よ…よくやった月、
これでお前の疑いは晴れたはずだ…
The suspicions against you should now be lifted.
That's right, Light-kun. We also believe that there's a second Kira.
その通りです月君
私達も「第二のキラ」だと見ています
As I thought...
やはり…
You already knew, Ryuuga? I mean.. Ryuuzaki.
分っていたのか流河、
…いや竜崎
You were testing me, weren't you?
わかっていて僕を、試したのか？
試したのではありません、
I wasn't testing you.
If I were the only one to have come up with the "second Kira" theory, people may have trouble believing me.
私一人が第二のキラ説を考えても説得力がない
Since you've come to the same conclusion as I did, it's become a much more convincing viewpoint.
月君が同じ推理をした事で、より有力の説となります
Light-kun, you really are extremely helpful.
月君は本当に力になる、
助かります
So, it's decided.
決まりですね
Firstly, we have to stop the second Kira.
まず第二のキラを止めなければなりません、
Evidently, they sympathize with Kira, but they aren't very intelligent.
奴は明らかにキラに共鳴しているし、そんなに賢くはない
They might even obey the real Kira.
本物のキラには従うかもしれません
Thus, there's a good chance that we might be able to stop them by sending them a message from the real Kira.
ならば、
こちらで本物のメッセージを偽造すれば止められる可能性は高い
Thus, there's a good chance that we might be able to stop them by sending them a message from the real Kira.
I'd have expected nothing less from you, Ryuuzaki.
流石だな竜崎、
I was also thinking of that as the best course of action.
僕もそれが一番いい手だと思っていた…
I'd like you, Light-kun, to play the real Kira.
そこで月君に…
本物のキラを演じて欲しいんです
M-Me?!
ぼ…僕が？
はい、
Yes. With your talent, it shouldn't be a problem.
月君くらいの才能があれば、こなせるはずです
Anyhow, we don't have a lot of time.
とにかく時間がない
Can you write a response from "Kira" ready to be aired on this evening's news?
夜のニュースで流せるよう、
キラからの呼びかけの原稿を作ってもらえますか？
You bastard...
コイツ…
Is this what you planned all along? Is that why you brought me here?
最初からこの役をやらせる為に、僕をここへ…
Ryuuzaki, is this okay?
竜崎、これでいいかな
I really think I became Kira, just for a moment.
キラになりきったつもりだけど
It's very good... but unless you take out the bit that says, "I don't mind if you kill L"... I'll die.
すごくよくできていますが、
「 L は殺していいが」という部分は取らないと…
私は死にます
Ah, yes. If I were in Kira's shoes, in the current situation, I'm sure I'd order L's death.
いや、キラになりきってみたら、
今の状況なら、絶対 L だけは殺せと指示すると思ってね
It's just a joke. You can change it to whatever you want.
軽いジョークだ、その部分は適当に直してくれ
Yes...
はい
Aihara-san, the report is ready.
相原さん、
原稿できました、お願いします
Aihara-san, the report is ready.
Okay!
よし！
A terrible thing has occurred!
大変なことになりました
In response to the videos sent in by Kira and aired on Sakura TV, messages have been received from another person claiming that they are the real Kira.
先日、さくらテレビにビデオを送り、放映させたキラに対して、
自分が本物だと言う、もう一人のキラが現れました
They have demanded that the message from the real Kira is broadcast on all TV channels.
そして、各テレビ局に、
「真のキラからのメッセージ」を放映させることを要求
Police Headquarters have agreed for the video to be broadcast.
警察庁は、このビデオに関して放映することを許可しています
Is this Kira? Or are they both Kira?
こちらがキラなのか、これもキラなのか
First, take a look at this video sent in by Kira.
まずこの…キラから送られてきたビデオをご覧下さい
I'm Kira.
キラです
Yay! I got a response from Kira!
やった！
キラが返事くれた
I am the real Kira, and those videos sent to Sakura TV were not from Kira.
私が真のキラであり、
先日のさくらテレビで放映されたビデオの主は、
I am the real Kira, and those videos sent to Sakura TV were not from Kira.
キラではありません
Currently, I will tolerate the actions of the one that is taking my name.
現時点では私を名乗った者に対し、
私に協力し、
私の代弁をしようとしたと寛大に受けとめています
They have worked on my behalf, and have tried to aid me.
However, taking the lives of innocent people is directly against my beliefs.
しかし、
罪のない者の命を奪ったりする事は、私の意思と反する
However, taking the lives of innocent people is directly against my beliefs.
If the person taking my name holds the same beliefs as I, and is willing to help me,
もし私を名乗った者が私に共感し、
協力する気持ちがあるならば、
they must stop acting impulsively, and learn to understand my true intentions.
勝手な行動は慎んで、まず私の意思を理解する事です
If you do not heed this warning, you will leave me with no choice but to pass judgement on you.
Let's see now... Video, video!
さあ、ビデオビデオ
この忠告を聞かず暴走するならば、そちらから裁きます
What are you planning on doing?
何する気だ？
Naturally, I'm gonna send a response to Kira right away!
もっちろん、すぐキラに返事出すのに決まってるじゃない
A few days later
Ryuuzaki! We've received a response from the second Kira!
竜崎、第二のキラから返事です
What?!
なに？
It's here!
来たか？
I'll bring the envelope and everything else over as soon as I can; for the moment, I'm sending a copy to your computer.
すぐ封筒ごとそちらへ持って行きますが、
とりあえず、コピーした影像をパソコンに流しておきます
Kira-san, thank you for your response.
キラさん、お返事ありがとうございます
I will do as you ask.
私はキラさんの言う通りにします
おお…
We did it!
やった
"I will do as you ask", huh?
「キラの言う通りにします」、か…
I can't tell whether I can use them or not...
使えるんだか使えないんだか…
If they truly understood Kira's feelings, they should have enforced L's appearance on TV, and killed him!
本当にキラの気持ちがわかる奴なら、
L のテレビ出演だけは強行して L を殺す
If they truly understood Kira's feelings, they should have enforced L's appearance on TV, and killed him!
Don't mess things up... Damn it!
こんなのに引っ掛かるな、くそっ…
私はキラさんに会いたい、
I want to meet you, Kira-san.
I don't believe that you have the eyes, but don't worry, I won't kill you.
キラさんは目を持ってないと思いますが、
私はキラさんを殺したりはしません、安心してください
馬…馬鹿かコイツ…
What is this idiot thinking?!
They're talking about the Shinigami's eyes on a video that's being broadcast to the entire nation!
世間に流れるビデオに、死神の目の事を…
"I don't believe that you have the eyes"? What is that supposed to mean?
今、「目を持ってない」って言ったよな…なんだ
Dunno...
さあ…
Please think of a way that we can meet without the police finding out.
何か警察の人にはわからない、会ういい方法を考えてください
Once we meet, we can confirm our identities by showing each other our Shinigami.
会った時は、
お互いの死神を見せ会えば、確認できます
Once we meet, we can confirm our identities by showing each other our Shinigami.
Shinigami?!
死神…
This person is hopeless... If I don't do something fast...
駄目だコイツ…
はやく、なんとかしないと…
What?!
なんだ!?
R-Ryuuzaki!!
竜…竜崎!!
Are you okay?
大丈夫ですか
S-Shinigami...
死、死神…
Are you trying to tell me... that such things exist?!
そんな物の存在を…認めろとでも言うのか…
S-Shinigami...
死神…
Are you trying to tell me.. that such things exist?!
そんな物の存在を、認めろとでも言うのか…
Surely not...
ま、まさか…
There's no way that they exist...
そんな物いるはずが…
He's right, Ryuuzaki. There's no way that Shinigami actually exist.
そうだよ竜崎、
死神が存在するなんてありえない
Kira used prisoners to write sentences about Shinigami...
キラも刑務所内の犯罪者に、
死神が存在するような文書を書かせていた
If that's true, shouldn't we consider this to be the work of the original Kira?
それならやはり、これも今までキラと考えるべきでは…
同じ人物だから、同じ言葉を…
The same words from the same person?
I doubt that, father.
それはないよ、父さん
The Kira we have dealt with until now wouldn't have replied to our video.
これが今までのキラなら、
僕達の作ったビデオに対して、返事をするはずがない
The real Kira wouldn't have bought this story. And they wouldn't have prevented L from going on TV to be killed.
本物がこんな作戦にわざと乗って、
L をテレビ出演させて殺すのを、止めさせるはずもない
Then, is there a possibility that the real Kira and the second Kira may already have joined forces, and are using the term "Shinigami" to confuse our investigation?
じゃあ…本物と第二のキラがもう繋がりを持っていて、
「死神」という言葉で、捜査の撹乱を狙っているのでは？
Then, is there a possibility that the real Kira and the second Kira may already have joined forces, and are using the term "Shinigami" to confuse our investigation?
I don't think there's any chance of that happening.
それもありえません
月君の言う通り、
Light-kun is correct. If Kira is involved, I doubt that they'd stop trying to kill me.
キラが繋がっているのなら、
私を殺すことを中止するとは思えません
This second Kira appears to be acting on their own interests, rather than Kira's beliefs.
第二のキラはキラの思想とは関係なく、
自分の想いで動いています
Basically, their desire to meet Kira.
つまり、「キラに会いたい」という想いです
Exactly.
その通りだ…
They are acting on their own curiosity about Kira.
キラへの興味で動いている…
Perhaps "Shinigami" is referring to their ability to kill.
ちから
死神というのは、殺人の能力を示しているんじゃないかな？
"Confirm our identities by showing each other our Shinigami", could mean that they'll confirm each other's identity by demonstrating their ability to kill.
「お互いの死神を見せ会えば確認できます」…と言うのは、
ちから
殺しの能力を見せ合い、確認すると考えればいい
"Confirm our identities by showing each other our Shinigami", could mean that they'll confirm each other's identity by demonstrating their ability to kill.
You could be right...
そうですね…
At the very least, we can consider "Shinigami" as a common term of some significance between Kira and the second Kira.
少なくとも死神という言葉は、
キラと第二のキラの間では共通し
意味の通る何かと考えられる
We need to try to clarify that.
それが何なのかもう少しはっきりさせる様仕向けましょう
So, will we reply again to guide them?
じゃあまた返事をして誘導するのか？
If we probe too deeply, they may realize that we know nothing, and that we aren't really Kira.
下手に探りを入れると、
こっちが何もわかっていないのを気づかれて、
If we probe too deeply, they may realize that we know nothing, and that we aren't really Kira.
キラじゃない事がバレる…
No. From now on, we'll leave it to Kira and the second Kira.
いえ、ここから先はキラと第二のキラに任せるんです
Leave it to them?
任せる？
I assume that having received a reply from Kira, the second Kira is now content about the current situation.
第二のキラは、キラから返事は来た事で、
今の状態に満足していると考えられます
They believe that they've successfully appealed to Kira.
キラに対し、自分をアピールする事に成功したと…
Plus, they are using words that only they would know the significance of.
そして両者間でしかわからない言葉を使っています
この返事を再び今日のさくらテレビの六時のニュースで流します
We'll repeat this reply on the 6:00pm news on Sakura TV.
The real Kira will be watching to view the interaction between the second Kira and the fake Kira that we've created.
当然キラも、我々の作ったキラと、
第二のキラのやりとりは気にして観ているはずです
The real Kira would want to avoid any contact between the second Kira and the police.
キラの立場からすれば、
第二のキラと警察の直接の接触などは避けたいはず
If we're lucky, we'll get a response from the real Kira this time.
もしかすると、
今度は本物のキラが返事をしてくるかもしれません
If we're lucky, we'll get a response from the real Kira this time.
But what if we don't receive a response from Kira?
でも、もしキラからの返事がなかったら…
Well... I've tried to think of what the second Kira would do in this situation, and...
その時第二のキラはどうするか考えてみたんですが…
they would probably tell the police and the public further information that Kira would not want them to know,
もっと警察や世間にキラがバラされたくない事を公表し、
to force Kira to seek an audience with them!
キラを焦らせ焚きつけ、自分に会わせようとする
This could be very interesting!
こうなれば面白い
It'll be even more interesting if Kira does fear such a response, and sends their own message by video.
それを恐れてキラが、
ビデオ等でメッセージを送ってきたらもっと面白い
If that does happen, we'll have more physical evidence against Kira.
そうすれば、キラの物的証拠を得られる可能性も高くなります
Then, for the time being, let us pursue the second Kira.
ではしばらくは、第二のキラの荷から追っていきましょう
いいねぇ
That's good.
That's it, that's it!
うん、そうそうそうそう
That's good. That's so hot, Misa-chan!
いいよ、いいよいいよ MISA ☆ちゃん
Brilliant!
最高
あ～疲れた…
I'm so tired... Being a model is all about having stamina.
モデルの仕事も体力消化なんだよね…
Hey, Rem?
ねぇ、レム
ん？
Can I ask you something?
ひとつ聞いていい？
What is it?
何だ
Shinigami need to have a Death Note.
死神はデスノートを持ってないとダメ、
For Shinigami to play with humans, they need to have two.
人間にデスノートを持たせて遊ぶには二冊必要…
The Shinigami, Ryuk, who gave a notebook to Kira, tricked the Shinigami Overlord and got a second notebook, right?
キラにノートを持たせたリュークは、
死神大王を騙して二冊目を手に入れたって事ね
That's right.
そう
Did you do that too?
じゃあレムも？
No. The Shinigami Overlord isn't that easy to trick.
違うよ
死神大王なんてそう簡単に騙せる相手じゃない
So, how did you manage it?
じゃあどうやって…
I'm rare in the Shinigami world.
私は死神界でも数少ない、
I'm one of the few who actually knows how to kill a Shinigami.
死神を殺す方法を知っている死神だから…
とでも言っておこう
Let's leave it at that.
へぇ～じゃあ死神殺してノート奪って、
それを海砂にくれたんだ
So, you killed a Shinigami, and gave Misa their notebook?
No... I didn't kill them.
違うな、殺したわけではない
I just happened to be there when a Shinigami died.
たまたま死ぬ死神がいて、そこに私が居合わせた…
Hey, tell me how to kill a Shinigami!
ねぇ、死神殺す方法、教えてよ
You mustn't tell anyone.
誰にも言うなよ…
The way to kill a Shinigami is... to make them fall in love with a human.
死神を殺す方法は…
人間に恋させる事だ
What a beautiful way to kill someone.
素敵な殺し方…
There was once a Shinigami named Jealous, who used to constantly gaze at one particular girl from his place in the Shinigami world.
死神界から、
ずっと一人の少女を眺めていた、ジェラスって死神がいてね
ジェラスは死神界から、
From the Shinigami world, Jealous was always, always watching that girl.
いつもいつも、その子を見ていた…
It's today, isn't it? That girl's life runs out...
今日だね、あの子の寿命…
She seems so full of life... I wonder why it's today...
元気そうなのに、なんで今日なんだろう…
I wonder... why today?
なんで、今日なんだろう…
私もどう死ぬのか気になって、一緒に眺める事にした
I also became curious as to how she would die, so I chose to watch with him.
She was walking alone late at night... and then..
その子は夜道を一人で歩いていた
その時だった…
Suddenly a man appeared from an alley, and confessed his love for the girl.
突然路地から一人の男が現れ、娘に告白した
I love you more than anyone in this world!!
僕は世界の誰よりも君を愛している
I want to watch over, and protect you forever!!
いつも君を見てる、守りたいんだよ君を…
The girl, having never seen the man before, naturally refused him.
見ず知らずの男、当然娘は断った
Then... I'll kill you... before killing myself!
じゃあ、君を殺して…
僕も死ぬーー!!
お、おい！
Hey! Stop that!!
やめないか！
Jealous did something that no Shinigami should ever do.
ジェラスは死神として、やってはならない事をした
Jealous used his Death Note to save that girl...
ジェラスはその娘を助ける為に、ノートを使ってしまった…
But that is not allowed.
でも駄目なんだよ
Shinigami exist solely to take human lives in order to increase their own.
死神は人間の寿命を短くする…頂く為だけに存在している
At that moment, Jealous turned into sand, or rust... something I couldn't identify... and died.
その瞬間、ジェラスは砂とも錆ともわからぬ物に変わり、
…死んだ
All that remained was the Death Note.
あとにはデスノートだけが残された…
Jealous's life was added to the lifespan of the girl he had been watching.
そしてジェラスの命が、
助けられた娘に見合った寿命として与えられたんだ
If he wasn't in love with that girl, he wouldn't have died?
その子に恋してなければ、死神は死ななかったってこと…？
That's right.
その通りだ
So, the person... who helped me back then... was Jealous, the Shinigami.
じゃああの時、
私を助けてくれたのは…ジェラスって死神だったんだ
So, the person... who helped me back then... was Jealous, the Shinigami.
そう、
Correct.
ジェラスはお前に恋をした
Jealous was in love with you.
That's why that notebook is yours.
だからそのノートは、お前の物だ
…うん
そうかぁ
I see. You've got to make a Shinigami fall in love and help someone.
死神殺すには人間に恋させて助けさせないとダメなんだ
What about you Rem? You aren't falling for me, are you?
レムはどう？
私に恋しちゃったりしてない？
Give it up. You can't kill me.
諦めな、
お前に私は殺せない
Give it up. You can't kill me.
あっ、バレてた？
Oh, so you guessed it?
But now I have something else I can tell Kira!
でもこれで、キラに教えてあげられる話がまたできたよ
知ってるのかな
I wonder if they know how to kill a Shinigami?
死神のこ．ろ．し．か．た♡
I told them on TV to think up a good way for us to meet each other, but I still haven't had a response...
テレビでも「会ういい方法考えてください」
ってちゃんと流してくれたのに、
なかなか返事こないな
Maybe I should say something again!
またこっちから何か言ってみようかな
This isn't good... There's no way I can leave the second Kira to their own devices.
まずい…
このまま第二のキラを放っておくわけにはいかない
This isn't good... There's no way I can leave the second Kira to their own devices.
If the second Kira makes a critical error, and gets captured by the police, there's a chance that they could find out about the Death Note.
第二のキラが致命的なヘマを犯し、
警察に捕まったりすれば、
デスノートのことがバレる可能性がある
If the second Kira makes a critical error, and gets captured by the police, there's a chance that they could find out about the Death Note.
Welcome.
いらっしゃいませ
A strawberry sundae please!
ストロベリーサンデーちょうだい
Coming right up.
かしこまりました
But how.. should I contact the second Kira without L noticing...
だがどうする…
L に気づかれることなく第二のキラに接触するには…
Sorry for the delay.
お待たせしました
あ～あ～、早く会いたいな、キラに
I can't wait to meet Kira!
Still... I wonder what they're like... fake Kira...
それにしても、一体どんな奴なんだ…
偽キラ
I wonder what they're like... Kira!
一体どんな人なのかな～キラって
To be continued
5月22日、青山でノートを見せ合う
もし偽キラが捕まった場合、
ノートだけでも僕がおさえなければ…
最悪、そこにいた者を含め殺すしかない